MIKE LOPEZ: Hi.
And now I'm going to discuss "Nightmare".
"Nightmare" is a very powerful card out of the black color.
It is a rare from the basic set.
It has always been a rare and it has been around for a long time.
So again, we have creature "Nightmare", which means it is a nightmare creature that gets benefits for anything that benefits nightmares.
"Nightmare" cost you 5 and a black, which means its converted mana cost is 6.
This means that you're getting a very big creature or a very cool creature, in which case this is both.
So again, as you see down here, "Nightmare" does not have power and toughness.
It has stars for power and toughness ought to be.
So again, this means that something on the card is going to tell you what these equal.
This creature has flying, which means they can only be blocked by flying creatures and/or creatures with reach and "Nightmare's" cool power is that its power and toughness are equal to each of the number of swamps you control, which means that if you have 6 swamps, if you play this with all black mana, then you at least have a 6/6 creature with flying, which means your mana production is perfectly equal for this card, and/or you could play this card in any multicolored deck, and you could still get pretty much even mana production as long as you have enough swamps to put enough power and toughness on them.
Also, this goes up every time you have a swamp so this has unlimited potential.
It's a very powerful card.